// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q006: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Dela Device emphasized the ease of use ------ the durability of its products at the New Tech Convention.',
      choices: ['in addition', 'equally', 'even though', 'as well as'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['as'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Mr. Ajayâ€™s extensive expertise in legal matters makes him the ------ person to lead the legal department.',
      choices: ['idealist', 'ideal', 'idealism', 'ideally'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['ideal'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Mountain View Inn operates a ------ shuttle to the airport as one of its services for guests.',
      choices: ['transparent', 'complimentary', 'fierce', 'protective'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['complimentary'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Watanabe ------ a promotion given her sales performance over the past two years.',
      choices: ['preserves', 'reduces', 'withstands', 'deserves'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['deserves'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Allen & Wolff LLP provides a ------ range of legal services to multinational companies.',
      choices: ['width', 'wide', 'widen', 'widely'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['wide'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ to the Baron Art Museum is free for children under 6 years old and seniors over 70 years old.',
      choices: ['Request', 'Compliance', 'Donation', 'Admission'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Admission'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Office cleaning services by Kambil Corporation in Detroit are ------ priced, so many local businesses are using them.',
      choices: ['reasonable', 'reasonably', 'reason', 'reasoning'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['reasonably'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Since its foundation, Works Uniforms has ------ in the sale of work clothing, footwear, and protective equipment for construction sites.',
      choices: ['promoted', 'assured', 'affected', 'specialized'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['specialized'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The sales meeting at the Hong Kong branch will be held tomorrow ------ at 10:00 a.m.',
      choices: ['reliably', 'potentially', 'relatively', 'promptly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['promptly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Green Forest Outdoors offers refunds on unused items ------ 7 days of purchase.',
      choices: ['before', 'from', 'within', 'until'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['within'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}